<tags>
  <item>
    <name>inverse.cgmap</name>
    <desc>
      Mapping file for analysis. Currently also during coarse-grained simulations, a mappin file has to be specified
      which is only a 1:1 mapping. This will change in the future.
    </desc>
  </item>
  <item>
    <name>non-bonded</name>
    <desc>
      Section for a non-bonded interaction. All sub-tags will be later on specified in 
      interaction.* since most of them are identical to bonded interactions.
    </desc>
  </item>
  <item>
    <name>bonded</name>
    <desc>
      Section for a bonded interaction. All sub-tags will be later on specified in 
      interaction.* since most of them are identical to non-bonded interactions.
    </desc>
  </item>
  
  <item>
    <name>interaction</name>
    <section/>
    <desc>fooo</desc>
  </item>

  <item>
    <name>interaction.name</name>
    <desc>
      Name of the interaction
    </desc>
  </item>
  <item>
   <name>interaction.inverse.target</name>
   <desc> target distribution (rdf), just give gromas rdf.xvg </desc>
  </item>
  <item>
   <name>interaction.type1</name>
    <desc>Only for non-bonded. Bead type 1 of non-bonded interaction.</desc>
  </item>
  <item>
   <name>interaction.type2</name>
    <desc>Only for non-bonded. Bead type 2 of non-bonded interaction.</desc>
  </item>
  <item>
    <name>interaction.min</name>
    <desc>lower bound of interval for potential table in which calculations are performed.</desc>
  </item>
  <item>
    <name>interaction.max</name>
    <desc>upper bound of interval for potential table in which calculations are performed.</desc>
  </item>
  <item>
    <name>interaction.step</name>
    <desc>step size of interval for potential table in which calculations are performed.</desc>
  </item>
  <item>
   <name>interaction.inverse.do_potential</name>
   <default>1</default>
   <desc>Update cacly for potential update. 1 means update, 0 don't update. 1 1 0 means update 2 iterations, then don't update, then repeated. </desc>
  </item>
  <item>
    <name>interaction.inverse.post_update</name>
    <desc>Additional post processing of dU before added to potential. This is a list of scripts which are called separated by space.</desc>
  </item>
  <item>
    <name>interaction.inverse.post_update_options</name>
    <desc>This sectioncontains all options for post update scripts.</desc>
  </item>
  <item>
    <name>interaction.inverse.post_add</name>
    <desc>Additional post processing of U after dU added to potential. See interaction.post_update for details.</desc>
  </item>
  <item>
    <name>interaction.inverse.imc</name>
    <desc>Section containing inverse monte carlo specific options.</desc>
  </item>
  <item>
    <name>interaction.inverse.imc.group</name>
    <desc>
      Group of interaction. Cross-correlations of all members of a group are taken into account for calculating the update.
        I no cross correlations should be calculated, interactions have to be put into different groujps.
    </desc>
  </item>
  <item>
    <name>interaction.inverse.gromacs</name>
    <desc>
        This section contains gromacs specific options if gromacs is used as simulatiion program.
    </desc>
  </item>
  
  <item>
    <name>interaction.inverse.gromacs.table</name>
    <desc>
      Name of file for tabulated potential of this interaction. This fill will be created from the internal tabulated potential format for every run.
    </desc>
  </item>  

  <item><name>inverse</name><section/><desc> general options for inverse script </desc></item>
  <item><name>inverse.p_target</name><desc> target pressure </desc></item>
  <item><name>inverse.kBT</name><desc> kBT (300*0.00831451 gromacs units) </desc></item>
  <item><name>inverse.program</name><desc>simulation package to be used (currently only gromacs) </desc></item>
  <item><name>inverse.gromacs</name><desc> gromacs specific options </desc></item>
  <item><name>inverse.gromacs.equi_time</name><default>0.0</default><desc> begin analysis after this time </desc></item>
  <item><name>inverse.gromacs.first_frame</name><default>0</default><desc> trash so many frames at the beginning </desc></item>
  <item><name>inverse.gromacs.table_bins</name><desc> grid for table*.xvg !</desc></item>
  <item><name>inverse.gromacs.pot_max</name><desc> cut the potential at this value (gromacs bug) </desc></item>
  <item><name>inverse.gromacs.table_extend</name><desc> extend the tables to this value </desc></item>
  <item><name>inverse.gromacs.topol</name><desc> topology + trajectory. Be careful, do not change yet! </desc></item>
  <item><name>inverse.gromacs.traj</name><desc> topology + trajectory. Be careful, do not change yet! </desc></item>
  <item><name>inverse.filelist</name><desc> these files are copied for each new run </desc></item>
  <item><name>inverse.iterations_max</name><desc> do so many iterations </desc></item>
  <item><name>inverse.method</name><desc> ibm: inverse boltzmann imc: inverse monte carlo </desc></item>
  <item><name>inverse.scriptdir</name><desc> directory for user scripts (e.g. \$PWD)</desc></item>
  <item><name>inverse.log_file</name><desc> write log to this file </desc></item>
  <item><name>inverse.imc</name><desc> general imc specific options </desc></item>
  <item><name>inverse.imc.solver</name><desc> solver to solve linear equation system, can be octave or matlab </desc></item>
</tags>
